A Guide to the John A. Hartford Foundation records, Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing and New York University, Nurses Improving Care for Healthsystem Elders (NICHE), Series 9 FA1721
Rockefeller Archive Center
John A. Hartford Foundation records, Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing and New York University, Nurses Improving Care for Healthsystem Elders (NICHE), Series 9
1997-2006
Rockefeller Archive Center
John A. Hartford Foundation
FA1721
52.57 Cubic Feet 40 standard record storage boxes.
Arrangement
Arranged as received
Scope and Contents
Geriatric Institutional Assessment Profile (GIAP), an instrument designed to help hospitals analyze the needs of their elderly patients and determine gaps in geriatric care provision. This series contains the original survey sheets collected from the hospitals and medical centers that worked with the John A. Hartford Foundation and the NICHE (Nurses Improving Care for Healthsystem Elders) program. Included with the original data surveys are some of the final analyses and presentations the John A. Hartford Foundation used in their program.
Biographical / Historical
The John A. Hartford Foundation (JAHF) was established in 1929 by brothers John and George Hartford, sons of the founder of the Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company (A and P). The foundation is a private, nonpartisan philanthropy dedicated to improving the care of older adults. For its first several decades, the foundation broadly supported clinical medical research. By 1982, it began to focus solely on geriatric healthcare. In 2015, JAHF paid out $20.2 million on a total of 80 active grants and committed $25.3 million to 24 new grants projects, all focused on the care of older adults.
- Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing and New York University, Nurses Improving Care for Healthsystem Elders (NICHE), 1997-2006; 9; 52.57 Cubic Feet
  - Miami Valley Hospital, D3, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 1)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, D4, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 1)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, D4, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 1)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, D4, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 1)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, D4, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 1)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, D5, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 1)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, D5, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 1)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, D5, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 2)
  - Miami Valley Hospital, D5, Nurses Improving Care for Health System Elders, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP) (Box 2)
  - Middlesex Medical Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 700-749 (Box 2)
  - Middlesex Medical Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 2)
  - Middlesex Medical Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 2)
  - Middlesex Medical Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 750-774 (Box 2)
  - Middlesex Medical Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 2)
  - Middlesex Medical Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 2)
  - Middlesex Medical Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 7500-7599 (Box 2)
  - Middlesex Medical Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 2)
  - Middlesex Medical Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 2)
  - Middlesex Medical Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 10400-10498 (Box 2)
  - Middlesex Medical Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 2)
  - Middlesex Medical Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 2)
  - Mission St. Joseph's Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 21164-25238 (Box 2)
  - Mission St. Joseph's Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 2)
  - Mission St. Joseph's Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 2)
  - Mission St. Joseph's Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 25241-25400 (Box 2)
  - Mission St. Joseph's Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 2)
  - Mission St. Joseph's Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 2)
  - Mission St. Joseph's Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 25406-25506 (Box 2)
  - Mission St. Joseph's Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 2)
  - Mission St. Joseph's Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 2)
  - Mission St. Joseph's Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 25513-25597 (Box 2)
  - Mission St. Joseph's Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 2)
  - Mission St. Joseph's Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 2)
  - North Iowa Mercy Hospital, Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Mercy Hospital, Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Mercy Hospital, Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Mercy Hospital, North Hampton, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Mercy Hospital, North Hampton, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Mercy Hospital, North Hampton, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Mercy Hospital, Palo Alto, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Mercy Hospital, Palo Alto, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Mercy Hospital, Palo Alto, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 198-275 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 276-408 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 412-493 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 494-566 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 567-631 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 633-90003 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 3)
  - North Iowa Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 3)
  - North Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 22700-22765 (Box 3)
  - North Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 3)
  - North Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 3)
  - North Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 22766-22833 (Box 3)
  - North Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 3)
  - North Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 3)
  - North Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 22834-22904 (Box 3)
  - North Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 3)
  - North Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 3)
  - North Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 1-2, 22905-22972 (Box 3)
  - North Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 3-4 (Box 3)
  - North Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 5 (Box 3)
  - North Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 22974-23042 (Box 3)
  - North Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 3)
  - North Memorial Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 3)
  - NYU Downtown Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 1 (Box 3)
  - NYU Downtown Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 2 (Box 3)
  - NYU (New York University) Downtown Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 3 (Box 4)
  - NYU (New York University) Downtown Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 4 (Box 4)
  - NYU (New York University)Downtown Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, Page 5 (Box 4)
  - Oakwood Small Hospital Affialiates, North Iowa Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 20700-20780 (Box 4)
  - Oakwood Small Hospital Affialiates,, North Iowa Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 4)
  - Oakwood Small Hospital Affialiates,North Iowa Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 4)
  - Oakwood Hospital, Big, North Iowa Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 20784-20997 (Box 4)
  - Oakwood Hospital, Big, North Iowa Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 4)
  - Oakwood Hospital, Big, North Iowa Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 4)
  - Oakwood Hospital, Big, North Iowa Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 20999-21088 (Box 4)
  - Oakwood Hospital, Big, North Iowa Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 4)
  - Oakwood Hospital, Big, North Iowa Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 4)
  - Oakwood Hospital, Big, North Iowa Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2 (Box 4)
  - Oakwood Hospital, Big, North Iowa Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 4)
  - Oakwood Hospital, Big, North Iowa Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 4)
  - Oakwood Hospital, Big, North Iowa Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1-2, 22693-22698 (Box 4)
  - Oakwood Hospital, Big, North Iowa Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3-4 (Box 4)
  - Oakwood Hospital, Big, North Iowa Mitchell County, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 4)
  - Foote Memorial Hospital, Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, 110001, D1 (Box 4)
  - Foote Memorial Hospital, Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, 110001, D2 (Box 4)
  - Foote Memorial Hospital, Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, 110001, D3 (Box 4)
  - Foote Memorial Hospital, Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, 110001, D4 (Box 5)
  - Foote Memorial Hospital, Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V4, 110001, D5 (Box 5)
  - Generose Medical Psychiatry 3E, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 1 (Box 5)
  - Generose Medical Psychiatry 3E, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 2 (Box 5)
  - Generose Medical Psychiatry 3E, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 3 (Box 5)
  - Generose Medical Psychiatry 3E, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 4 (Box 5)
  - Generose Medical Psychiatry 3E, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), Page 5 (Box 5)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 114342-114726 (Box 5)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4, 114342-114723 (Box 5)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4, 114724-115349 (Box 5)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5, 114342-114723 (Box 5)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5, 114724-115349 (Box 5)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 114342-114722 (Box 6)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 114724-115349 (Box 6)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 115030-114999 (Box 6)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 114687-115029 (Box 6)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 114342-114686 (Box 6)
  - Good Samaritan Hospital, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 114727-115349 (Box 6)
  - Bronson Methodist, Catholic Health Partners, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4, 110421-110989 (Box 6)
  - Bronson Methodist, Catholic Health Partners, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 110000-110300 (Box 6)
  - Bronson Methodist, Catholic Health Partners, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 110000-110300 (Box 7)
  - Bronson Methodist, Catholic Health Partners, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 110000-110300 (Box 7)
  - Bronson Methodist, Catholic Health Partners, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 110421-111007 (Box 7)
  - Bronson Methodist, Catholic Health Partners, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 110421-110999 (Box 7)
  - Bronson Methodist, Catholic Health Partners, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 110421-110999 (Box 7)
  - Bronson Methodist, Catholic Health Partners, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D1, 108000-108636 (Box 7)
  - Bronson Methodist, Catholic Health Partners, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 108000-108636 (Box 7)
  - Bronson Methodist, Catholic Health Partners, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D2, 108001-108315 (Box 7)
  - Bronson Methodist, Catholic Health Partners, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D3, 108001-108636 (Box 7)
  - Bronson Methodist, Catholic Health Partners, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D4, 108001-108636 (Box 8)
  - Bronson Methodist, Catholic Health Partners, Post Test, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), D5, 108001-108636 (Box 8)
  - Catholic Health Partners, Administrative (Box 8)
  - Catholic Health Partners, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 1-2, 20918-27389 (Box 8)
  - Catholic Health Partners, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 3-4, 20918-27389 (Box 8)
  - Catholic Health Partners, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 5, 20918-27389 (Box 8)
  - Catholic Health Partners,Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 1-2, 27390-27467 (Box 8)
  - Catholic Health Partners, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 3-4, 27390-27467 (Box 8)
  - Catholic Health Partners, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 5, 27390-27467 (Box 8)
  - Catholic Health Partners, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 1-2, 27479-27663 (Box 8)
  - Catholic Health Partners, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 3-4, 27479-27663 (Box 8)
  - Catholic Health Partners, Nurses Improving Care to the Hospitalized Elderly, Geriatric Institutional Assessent Profile (GIAP), V2, Page 5, 27479-27663 (Box 8)